Deborah Rimei



PERSONAL PROFILE

Second-year BSCH Computing Science student with 2 years of experience in customer service and data administration. Demonstrated ability to code with diverse programming languages including Java and JavaScript. Organized and meticulous individual, determined to expand my insights in technology and work with a team of professional.

KEY SKILLS

- Programming languages: Java, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, ReactJs, SQL.
- MS Office: proficient in Excel spreadsheets and formulas, familiar with Word and PowerPoint
- Organizational: successfully passed the first year of college while working full-time. Able
 to prioritize tasks both at work and in life and meet deadlines.
- Meticulous
- Client oriented: deep attention to the customer build during my 4+ summer seasons working as receptionist in hotel.

EDUCATION HISTORY

2019 - 2023

BSc (Hons) Computing Science, Griffith College 1st year PPA 85%

Main Subjects:

- Object Oriented programming Java
- Web Design HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Software Development Java, GitLab
- Relational Databases SQL
- Computer hardware
- System Analysis and Design

2009 - 2014

 $\label{eq:high-school-polo} \textbf{High School Diploma-ITT Marco Polo, Institute for Tourism}$

Rimini, Italy

Top subjects: maths, economics, languages. Average grade: 8.0/10.0

WORKING EXPERIENCE

2019 - present

Discount Administrator, UPS (United Parcel Services)

- Responsible to amend invoices amount by applying correct discounts
- High attention to detail required in order to provide the correct calculation with appropriate discounts
- Excellent organization skills in prioritizing assignment tasks and escalation from Management, providing necessary documents and coversheet on time
- Communicate with internal and external operators in a clear and concise manner

2018 - 2019

Customer Billing Representative, UPS (United Parcel Services)

- Communicating with customers through phone and emails in a clear and professional manner
- Responding promptly to inquire, logging-in cases in the system when required
- Excellent knowledge of the system and company protocols for the resolution of customer issues/cases
- Maintaining a positive and empathic attitude towards customer and team mates

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES

Technology. I am passionate about coding, specifically with Java, and find the best solution to problems

Environment. Deeply care about our natural environment and the impact we have on flora and fauna. Trying to live fully sustainably by making small conscious choices every day.

Reading. I like reading books that stimulate my thinking and make me grow professionally and as a better individual. My favourite genres: self-help, biography, spiritual, business.

Sport: Enjoy cycling and keeping myself fit by doing long walks or regular exercises.

REFERENCES: Available upon request.